Am I the asshole for suspecting m
y parrot being a Nazi sympathizer
?
Post.
So last week I bought a parrot fo
r my living room.
My wife thought it was a little s
illy but I thought it was cute an
d a nice addition to
the family.
But yesterday my wife overheard t
he parrot calling and repeating s
omething about, mine
furor.
I know that's German and I've bee
n watching a lot of, 93 hunt for
the red October, 94
recently, so I assume it's referr
ing to Hitler.
Today my wife tried to get it to
say something else and it respond
ed with, Deutsche Land
Uber Alice.
I know it's just a parrot and the
y're known to mimic things they h
ear, but it's starting
to creep me out a little.
Should I be worried and get rid o
f the parrot or am I just overthi
nking things?
Am I the asshole for suspecting i
t's a Nazi sympathizer?