Am I the Asshole for Breaking  Up with Him Over His  Hot Dog Habit? I met this amazing
guy a few months
ago
We hit it
off right away and
had an amazing first
couple of dates
We
started seeing each other
more often, and things
were really good ,
until I noticed something
strange
:Every time
I went to his
house, he was eating
a hot dog
Just
one hot dog
Every
single time
I couldn't
believe it
:At
first I tried not
to be too judgmental
, but it got
to a point where
I was getting really
annoyed
I 'd try
to talk to him
while he was eating,
and he'd just be
picking at his hot
dog the whole time
:I was getting
frustrated, so I eventually
talked to him about
it
He just
kind of laughed and
said it was no
big deal
So I
broke up with him
:Now friends are telling
me I'm being an
asshole
Was I out
of line for ending
our relationship just because
he ate a hot
dog every day?