Am I the asshole for sunshine sha
ming my cousin?
So my cousin and I are very close
.
We both live in different cities,
but we try to stay in touch as m
uch as possible.
However, lately he's been extreme
ly negative on social media, repl
ying to all posts with
snarky comments, and seems to be
intent on ruining everyone's sunn
y days.
I've tried to talk to him about i
t, but he's just brushed it off,
saying he's just having
a bad day.
I don't think it's just a bad day
, though.
So today I decided to take matter
s into my own hands and post a pi
cture of the beautiful
beach by my house, captioning it
with something about how nice the
weather is and how grateful
I am.
He responded with a snarky commen
t, something like, thanks for the
sunshine shaming.
I felt like he was really overste
pping his boundaries and that he
was just trying to make
everyone around him as miserable
as he is.
Am I the asshole for posting the
beach picture?